Inventory of the Richard Throssel Papers, 1900-1993 (bulk 1902-1933)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Photographs and Negatives, 1902-ca. 1920s; Series I.; 14.86 cubic ft. (6 letter boxes, 1 F24 box, 39 negative boxes, 5 shoe boxes and 4 F20 boxes).
  - 8x10 and 5 x 7 Glass Plate Negatives and Photographs, Subseries I.
    - "Two Old Timers" (Box 1, Folder 24)
      TP202
      Throssel ID #6900 "©"07
      Throssel #317
    - The Sentinel Variation (Box 1, Folder 25)
      TP203 and TP203A
      Throssel ID #6885 "©"07
      Throssel #318
    - "The Sentinel" (Box 1, Folder 25)
      TP204
      AHC Neg. #25153
      Throssel ID #6884 "©"07
      Throssel #319
      9 prints
      4 nitrate negatives 6½ x 8½
    - Man on Horseback (Possibly Corresponding to "The Sentinel") (Box 1, Folder 26)
      TP205
    - Man on Horseback (Possibly Corresponding to "The Sentinel") (Box 1, Folder 26)
      TP205A
    - "The Advance Scouts" (Box 1, Folder 26)
      TP206
      Throssel ID #6953 "©"08
      6 prints
    - Four Bareback Riders (Box 1, Folder 26)
      TP207
      AHC Neg. #24268
      Throssel #416
    - "The Advance Scouts" (Box 1, Folder 26)
      TP208
      Throssel #417
    - Agent S.G. Reynolds and Family (Box 1, Folder 27)
      TP209
      Throssel #421
    - Crow Procession Through Camp - Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 27)
      TP210
      Throssel #422
    - White Man on Horseback - Unidentified (Box 1, Folder 27)
      TP211
      Throssel #423
    - Riders/Event (Box 1, Folder 27)
      TP212
      AHC Neg. #19253
      Throssel #425
    - Riders/Event (Box 1, Folder 27)
      TP213
      Negative Box 19
      Throssel #426
    - Crow Children on Horses (Box 1, Folder 27)
      TP214
      Throssel ID #6809 "©"07
      Throssel #427
    - "Little Iron Horse" Crow Girl (Box 1, Folder 27)
      TP215
      AHC Neg. #25154
      Throssel ID #8V006 "©"05
      Throssel #428
    - "Up Pryor Canyon" (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP216
      AHC Neg. #25709
      Throssel ID #6861 "©"07
      Throssel #429
    - "Up Pryor Canyon" (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP216A
    - "Going to Water" (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP217 and TP217A
      Throssel ID #6V010
    - "Going to Water" - Variation (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP218
    - "The Buffalo" and Variations (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP219
      Throssel ID #4502 (?)
    - "The Buffalo" and Variations (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP219A
    - "The Buffalo" and Variations (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP219B
    - "The Buffalo" and Variations (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP219C
      2 glass positives 4 x 5
    - "The Buffalo" and Variations (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP219D
    - "A Race that is Vanquished" (Buffalo) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP220
    - "A Race that is Vanquished" (Buffalo) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      TP220A
    - Parade (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP221
      Throssel #424
    - Parade (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP222
      Throssel #435
    - "Watching Division of Beef" (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP223
      Throssel #436
    - Riders (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP224
      Throssel #437
    - Crow Tribal Police (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP225
      Throssel #438
    - Parade (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP226
      Throssel #439
    - Parade (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP227 and TP227A
      Throssel #440
    - Riders (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP228
      Throssel #441
      1 lantern slide 3 x 4 (broken)
    - Warriors on Horseback (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP229 and TP229A
      Negative Box 20
      Throssel #442
    - Warriors on Horseback (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP230
      Throssel #443
    - Warriors on Horseback (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP230A
      Throssel #443A
    - Warriors on Horseback (Box 2, Folder 2)
      TP230B
      AHC Neg. #25727
      Throssel #444
    - "Leaving Camp" (Box 2, Folder 3)
      TP231
      Throssel #445
    - Parade (Box 2, Folder 3)
      TP232
      Throssel #446
    - Riders - Posed (Box 2, Folder 3)
      TP233
      Throssel #447
    - Parade Float (Box 2, Folder 3)
      TP234
      Throssel #448
    - "Reb War Party - Plenty Coups - Old Historian" (Box 2, Folder 3)
      TP235
      Throssel #449
    - "The Feathered Horsemen - Sioux" (Box 2, Folder 3)
      TP236
      Throssel ID #6883 "©" 07
      Throssel #450
    - "The Returning Warriors" (Box 2, Folder 3)
      TP237 and TP237A
      Throssel ID #6869 "©" 07
      Throssel #451
    - Riders -Posed (Box 2, Folder 3)
      TP238
      Throssel #452
    - "The Parade of Victory" (Box 2, Folder 4)
      TP239
      Throssel #453
    - Riders in Formation (Box 2, Folder 4)
      TP240
      Throssel #454
    - Riders (Box 2, Folder 4)
      TP241
      Throssel #455
    - Riders (Box 2, Folder 4)
      TP242
      Throssel #456
    - "A War Party" (Box 2, Folder 4)
      TP243
      Throssel #457
      2 nitrate positives 6½ x 8½
    - Richard Throssel - Portrait (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP244
      AHC Neg. #24905, Negative Box 20
    - "White Swan" Crow (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP245
      Throssel ID #1908
      Throssel #430
    - "White Swan" Crow (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP246
      Throssel #431
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP247 and TP247A
      2 glass negatives 4 x 5
    - "Sitting Eagle" Crow (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP248
      Throssel #432
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP249
      Negative Box 21
      Throssel #433
    - "Harry Don't Mix" Crow (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP250
      Throssel #434
    - "Prairie Bird" Crow (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP251
      Throssel ID #6P007 "©" 05
      Throssel #462
    - "Prairie Bird" Crow (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP252 and TP252A
      AHC Neg. #19191
      Throssel ID #6P008 "©" 05
      Throssel #463
    - Boy - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP253
      Throssel #464
    - "Papoosie Iron Horse" (Beth Iron Horse) (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP254
      Throssel #465
    - "Deer Woman" (Crow girl) (Box 2, Folder 5)
      TP255
      AHC Neg. #15673
      Throssel #468
    - Crow Girl (Box 2, Folder 6)
      TP256
      Throssel #466
    - "Deer Woman" (Crow girl) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      TP257
      Throssel #467
    - "Deer Woman" (Crow) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      TP258
      Throssel #469
    - Crow Girl with Doll (Box 2, Folder 6)
      TP259
      AHC Neg. #15672
      Throssel #470
    - Crow Girl (Box 2, Folder 6)
      TP260
      AHC Neg. #15671
      Throssel #471
    - "A Cheyenne Warrior" (Cheyenne Boy) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      TP261
      Throssel ID #6903 "©" 07
      Throssel #472
    - "Baby Stuart" Crow (an Indian girl with dog) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      TP262
      AHC Neg. #15654
      Throssel ID #0109
      Throssel #473
      1 negative image print
      3 nitrate positives 6½ x 8½
    - Sitting Bird - Crow (Box 2, Folder 7)
      TP263
      AHC Neg. #19184
      Throssel #476
    - Wife of "Cuts the Bear's Ears" Crow (Box 2, Folder 7)
      TP264
      AHC Neg. #15670
      Throssel #477
    - "Mary Lincoln" - Wife of Albert, Mother of Winnie Lincoln (Crow) (Box 2, Folder 7)
      TP265
      Throssel #478
    - "Julia" Crow (Box 2, Folder 7)
      TP266
      Throssel #479
    - Woman - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 7)
      TP267
      AHC Neg. #15667
      Throssel #480
    - "The Old Historian" Crow (Bull Goes Hunting) (Box 2, Folder 7)
      TP268
      AHC Neg. #25917
      Throssel #481
    - "Bull Goes Hunting" Crow (Box 2, Folder 7)
      TP269
      Negative Box 22
      AHC Neg. #15632
      Throssel ID #6801 "©"06
      Throssel #675
    - "Pretty Medicine Pipe" Crow (Box 2, Folder 8)
      TP270
      Throssel ID #6P005 "©"05
      Throssel #482
    - "Pretty Hail" Crow (Box 2, Folder 8)
      TP271
      Throssel ID #6P004
      Throssel #483
    - "Strikes The Iron" Crow (Wife of Plenty Coups) (Box 2, Folder 8)
      TP272
      Throssel #484
    - "Pretty Shield" Crow (Box 2, Folder 8)
      TP273
      Throssel #485
    - "The First Mrs. Spotted Rabbit" Crow (Box 2, Folder 8)
      TP274
      Throssel #486
    - "Tillie Sings" or "Goes Together" Crow (Box 2, Folder 8)
      TP275
      Throssel ID #6803
      Throssel #487
    - "Pretty Shield" Crow (Box 2, Folder 8)
      TP276
      Throssel #488
    - "Wife of One Goose" Crow (Box 2, Folder 8)
      TP277
      Throssel ID #6855 "©"07
      Throssel #489
    - Crow Chief Plenty Coups in Front of his House (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP278
    - Plenty Coups Holding Book, American (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP279
      Throssel #474
    - Plenty Coups Holding Book, American (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP279A
      AHC Neg. #24270, Negative Box 22
    - "Plenty Coups" (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP280
      Throssel #609
    - Plenty Coups" (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP281
      Throssel #722
    - "Plenty Coups" (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP282
      Throssel #723
    - "Plenty Coups" (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP283
      Throssel #723A
    - "Plenty Coups" (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP284
      Throssel #723B
    - "Chief Gall" (Barry Image) (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP285
      Throssel #490
    - Woman - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP286
      Throssel #491
    - "Carries the War Staff" Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 9)
      TP287
      AHC Neg. #25711
      AHC Neg. #25651
      Throssel ID #6997
      Throssel #492
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP288
      Throssel #493
    - Man - Unidentified (Sioux?) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP289
      Throssel #494
    - "Barton" (Cheyenne or Sioux Woman) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP290
      AHC Neg. #15675
      Throssel ID #6X019
      Throssel #495
    - "Barton" (Indian Women) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP291
      Throssel #496
    - "Barton" (Indian Women) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP292
      Throssel ID #6905 "©"07
      Throssel #497
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP293
      Negative Box 23
      Throssel #498
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP294
      Throssel #499
    - (Crow Woman) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP295
      Throssel #499A
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP296
      Throssel #573
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 10)
      TP297
      Throssel #500
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP298
      Throssel #501
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP298A
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP299
      Throssel #502
    - Woman - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP300
      Throssel #503
    - "Carries the War Staff" (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP301
      Throssel #504
    - Woman - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP302
      Throssel #505
    - "Tillie" Crow (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP303
      Throssel #506
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP304
      Throssel #507
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP305
      Throssel #508
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP306
      Throssel #509
    - "Rose Bompard Bird" (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP307
      Throssel ID #6P006
      Throssel #510
    - "Rose Bompard Bird" (Box 2, Folder 11)
      TP308
      Throssel ID #6X018
      Throssel #701
    - "Takes Her Horse" [?] Crow (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP309
      Throssel #511
    - "Clara White Hip" [?] Crow (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP310
      Throssel #512
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP311 and TP311A
      Throssel #513
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP312
      Throssel #514
    - "Rides a Sorrel Horse" Crow (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP313
      Throssel #515
    - "Rides a Sorrel Horse" Crow (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP313A and TP313B
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP314
    - Woman - Old (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP315
      AHC Neg. #15662
      Throssel #516
    - Woman Covered with Indian Blanket - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP315A
    - Man-Not Crow (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP316
      Throssel #517
    - "Knows The Ground" Crow (Box 2, Folder 12)
      TP317
      Negative Box 24
      Throssel #518
    - "Albert Lincoln" Crow (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP318
      Throssel #519
    - "Albert Lincoln" Crow (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP319
      Throssel #520
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP320
      Throssel #522
    - Man-Not Crow (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP321
      Throssel #523
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP322
      Throssel #524
    - "White Hawk" [?] Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP323
      Throssel #525
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP324
      Throssel #526
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP325
      Throssel #527
    - "White Hawk" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP326
      Throssel #528
    - "Young Red Cloud" Sioux (Box 2, Folder 13)
      TP327
      Throssel #529
    - Man - Unidentified - Not Crow (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP328
      Throssel #530
    - Man - Unidentified - Not Crow (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP328A
      Throssel #530A
    - "Shot In the Hand" (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP329
      Throssel #531
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP330 and TP330A
      Throssel #532
    - Tall Whiteman (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP331
      Throssel #533
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP332
      Throssel #534
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP333
      Throssel #535
    - Crow Woman (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP334
      Throssel #536
    - Woman - Not Crow (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP335
      Throssel #538
      1 glass negative 7 x 6
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 14)
      TP336
      Throssel #539
    - Man - Unidentified - "The Old Chief's Face was Carved by Many Lines of Care" (Ookeas Illustration) (Box 2, Folder 15)
      TP337
      Throssel #540
      3 glass negatives 6½ x 8½
    - Non-Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 15)
      TP338
      Throssel #541
    - "Plenty Coups" (Box 2, Folder 15)
      TP339 and TP339A
      Throssel #542
      1 glass positive 5 x 7 (broken)
    - Non-Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 15)
      TP340 and TP340A
      Negative Box 25
      Throssel #543
    - "Long Otter" Crow (Box 2, Folder 15)
      TP341
      AHC Neg. #20453
      Throssel #546
    - Woman - Unidentified - not Crow (Box 2, Folder 15)
      TP342
      Throssel #547
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 15)
      TP343
      Throssel #548
    - "Two Leggings" Crow (Box 2, Folder 15)
      TP344
      Throssel #549
    - "White Hawk" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP345
      Throssel #550
    - "Two Leggings" Crow (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP346
      Throssel ID #6852 "©"07
      Throssel #554
    - "Other Medicine" Crow (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP347 and TP347
      Throssel ID #8P005 "©"05
      Throssel #555
    - "Two Leggings" Crow (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP348
      Throssel #559
    - "Boo Ah Xeesh" (Fish Swims) Crow (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP349
      Throssel #560
    - "White Swan" Crow - War Bonnet Not Crow (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP350
      Throssel #562
    - "Hillside" Crow (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP351
      Throssel #563
    - Man - Unidentified - Not Crow (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP352
      Throssel ID #8P001 "©"05
      Throssel #564
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP353
      Throssel #600
      1 glass negative 4 x 5 (broken)
    - "Bites" Not Crow (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP354
      Throssel ID #6904 "©"07
      Throssel #606
    - "Indian Mother Holding Cradle and Papoose" (Cheyenne-Wanamaker Print) (Box 2, Folder 16)
      TP355
      Throssel #607
    - "Plenty Coups" and "Bull Snake" Crow (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP356
      Throssel #608
    - "Plenty Coups" (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP357
      AHC Neg. #25700
      Throssel #694
    - Cuts The Bear's Ears (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP358
      Throssel #610
    - Cuts The Bear's Ears (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP358A
      Throssel #521
    - "White Man Runs Him" (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP359
      AHC Neg. #18600
      Throssel #611
    - "White Man Runs Him" (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP359A
      1 nitrate negative 4 x 5
    - "White Man Runs Him" (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP360
      Throssel ID #6P002 "©"05
      Throssel #631
    - "White Man Runs Him" (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP361
      Throssel #631A
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 17)
      TP362
      Throssel #612
    - "Little Wolf" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 18)
      TP363
      AHC Neg. #19186
      Throssel #613
    - "Little Wolf" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 18)
      TP364 and TP364A
      AHC Neg. #15631
      AHC Neg. #19250
      Throssel ID #6908 "©"07
      Throssel #614/623
      1 reverse image print
    - "Bobtail Horse" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 18)
      TP365
      Negative Box 26
      Throssel #615
    - "Bobtail Horse" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 18)
      TP366
      Throssel #679
    - "Plenty Coups" (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP367
      Throssel #616
    - "Tall Whiteman" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP368
      AHC Neg. #25708
      AHC Neg. #15669
      Throssel ID #6943 "©"08
      Throssel #617
      1 glass positive 5½ x 7½
    - "Tall Whiteman" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP369
      Throssel #624
    - "Bear _?_ Cloud" (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP370
      Throssel ID #6915 "©"07
      Throssel #618
    - Man - Unidentified - Crow [?] (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP371
      Throssel #619
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP372
      Throssel #620
    - Man - Unidentified - Not Crow [?] (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP373 and TP373A
      Throssel #621
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP374
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 19)
      TP375
      Throssel #622
    - Man - Unidentified - not Crow (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP376
      Throssel #625
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP377
      Throssel ID #6970 "©"09
      Throssel #626
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP378 and TP 378A
      Throssel #627
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP379
      Throssel #628
    - Man - Unidentified - not Crow (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP380
      Throssel ID #6848 "©"07
      Throssel #629
    - "Crazy Head" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP381
      Throssel ID #6948 "©"08
      Throssel #630
    - Man - Unidentified - "Bear _?_ Cloud"[?] - not Crow (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP382
      Negative Box 27
      Throssel #632
    - Man - Unidentified - Piegan[?] (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP383
      Throssel #633
      1 glass negative
    - "Two Leggings"[?] (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP384
      Throssel #634
    - "Young Red Cloud" Sioux (Box 2, Folder 20)
      TP385
      AHC Neg. #15663
      Throssel #636
      1 glass negative 8¼ x 4¼
    - "Young Hairy Wolf" (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP386
      Throssel #637
    - "Plenty Buffalo" Crow (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP387
      Throssel ID #8P006
      Throssel #638
    - "Young??" (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP388
      Throssel #639
    - "Cuts the Bear's Ears" Crow (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP389
      Throssel #640
    - "Cuts The Bear's Ears" and Wife (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP390
      Throssel #731
    - "Cuts the Bear's Ears" (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP391
      Throssel #732
    - "White Swan" Crow (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP392
      Throssel #641
    - "Does Everything" (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP393
      Throssel #642
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP394
      Throssel #643
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 21)
      TP395
      Throssel #644
    - "Short Bull" (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP396
      Throssel ID #8P003 "©"05
      Throssel #645
    - "Short Bull" (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP396A
    - "Short Bull" (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP397
      Throssel #545
    - "Horse Turns Back" - not Crow (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP398
      Throssel ID #6804 "©"07
      Throssel #646
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP399
      Throssel ID #8P007 "©"05
      Throssel #647
    - (Man - Unidentified) (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP400
    - "Two Leggings" Crow (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP401
      Throssel #653
    - "Two Leggings" Crow (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP402
      Throssel ID #6851 "©"07
      Throssel #654
    - "Two Leggings" Crow (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP403
      Negative Box 55
      Throssel #654A
    - "Two Moons" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP404, TP404A, and TP404B
      Throssel ID #6917 "©"07
      Throssel #553
    - "Two Moons" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP405
      Negative Box 28
      Throssel ID #6909 "©"07
      Throssel #635
    - "Two Moons" Cheyenne (Box 2, Folder 22)
      TP406
      Throssel ID #6910 "©"07
      Throssel #660
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP407
      Throssel #650
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP408
      Throssel #651
    - "Packs the Hat" Crow (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP409
      Throssel #652
    - "Plenty Coups" Crow (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP410
      Throssel #655
    - "Albert Lincoln" Crow (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP411
      Throssel #656
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP412
      Throssel #657
    - Woman - Unidentified - not Crow (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP413
      Throssel #658
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP414
      Throssel #659
    - "Long Otter" Crow (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP415
      Throssel #662
    - "Long Otter" Crow (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP415A
    - "Little Fire" Crow (Box 2, Folder 23)
      TP416
      AHC Neg. #15665
      Throssel #663
    - "Little Man" or "Walking Elk" (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP417
      Throssel ID #6856 "©"07
      Throssel #664
    - "White Man Runs Him" Crow (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP418
      Throssel #665
    - Crow Man (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP419
      Throssel #666
    - Man - Unidentified - not Crow [?] (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP420
      Throssel #667
    - "Two Leggings" Crow (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP421
      Throssel #668
    - "White Man Runs Him" Crow (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP422
      Throssel #669
    - "Other Medicine" Crow (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP423
      Throssel #670
      2 glass negatives 8 x 10 (broken)
    - "Plenty Hawk" Crow (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP424
      Throssel #671
    - "Hairy Moccasin" Crow (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP425
      Negative Box 28 and 29
      Throssel ID #6847 "©"08
      Throssel #672
    - "White Arm" Crow (Box 2, Folder 24)
      TP426
      Negative Box 29
      Throssel ID #6807 "©"07
      Throssel #673
    - Throssel [?] (per alberta throssel) (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP427
      Throssel ID #6911 "©"07
      Throssel #674
    - "Mint" Crow (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP428
      Throssel #676
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP429
      Throssel #677
    - "Striking Bear" Crow (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP430
      Throssel #678
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP431
      Throssel #551
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP432
      Throssel #552
    - "Wolf" Crow (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP433
      Throssel #556
    - "Wolf" Crow (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP434
      Throssel #561
    - "Wolf" Crow (Box 2, Folder 25)
      TP435
      Throssel #692
    - "Medicine Crow" Crow (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP436
      Throssel ID #6922 "©"08
      Throssel #557
    - "Medicine Crow" Crow (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP436A
      Throssel ID #6922 "©"08 (?)
      Throssel #661
    - "Young Hairy Wolf" (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP437
      Throssel #558
    - "Horse Goes Ahead" or "Two Leggings" (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP438
      Throssel ID #6X028 1911
    - Two Crow Girls with Dog (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP439
      AHC Neg. #18571
      AHC Neg. #18597
      AHC Neg. #25726
      AHC Neg. #25726X
      Throssel ID #8P002 "©"05
      Throssel #697
    - Two Girls - Probably Crow (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP440
      AHC Neg. #19182
      Throssel #698
    - Two Crow Girls with Dog (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP441
      Throssel #699
    - Man, Pipe, Medicine Tipi (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP442
      Negative Box 30
      Throssel ID #6950 "©"08
      Throssel #702
    - Crow Man and Woman (Box 3, Folder 1)
      TP443
      Throssel #704
    - Crow Man (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP444
      Throssel ID #6X001
      Throssel #680